A person insures his vehicles for two
purposes, first to avoid a police challan
and second, if the vehicle is damaged, it can be
compensated by the insurance company. The
insurance company Adani promises
that the
insurance company will compensate for all the damage caused to your vehicle, but the
real story begins
after the accident. If your vehicle is involved in an accident or caused by someone,
and when you reach the insurance company, the
insurance advisor,
after calculation, tells you that you will have to pay so much
money, but the story starts from there. So,
we had taken a policy, then there are
many things in the comprehensive insurance policy too, and the
appointed companies tell us which
add-ons
are available and the benefits of taking them.
[Music]
Immediately, the most important cover in the add-on kit of the companies is the
exhaust system cover. The
value of everything diminishes with time. Something
similar happens with your vehicle.
Whenever the insurance companies insure your vehicle,
and from that time till the time your vehicle
unfortunately meets with an accident, at the
time of its repair, the cost of that cover is always there.  After calculating the depreciation cost, they make
you pay for it.
In some things it is 30% and
in some things it is up to 40%. For plastic and
glass items, you have to decide the cost up to 50%.
If you make an
insurance policy in the form of Don't Comer, then
you do not have to pay a single penny. The
second most important is roadside assistance. If
you do this with your vehicle, sometimes the
tyre of the vehicle gets punctured, sometimes there is an accident, sometimes due to
road distance
problem, insurance companies
also give you assistance on the roadside, like if you have to
tow the vehicle, now the valve gets punctured or the
battery of your vehicle is not able to start
or you need fuel there, then
such systems are
given to you by the insurance companies through this Don't Comer.
After this, the third most important don't cover is
engine protection. Actually, in any insurance
policy, instant damage to the vehicle is covered, which is
not covered. Like, if the
engine of your vehicle gets
damaged due to an accident, the insurance of the vehicle is
not covered and through this,
insurance can be covered,
in the form of that, it also gets protection.
Business means if you have not taken any claim
during one year after insurance of your vehicle, then the
insurance tells you in the form of a report
that if you
take insurance next year, then you will get some
subscription that if you
take insurance claim up to 50%, there will be no
reduction in it and it is said that
through this you can also add it to it
and compensate for it. The
insurance company is not bound to compensate for the damage caused to the vehicle other than placement accident. If you
take tyre replacement as a shield, then the
insurance companies compensate for the damage caused on time by replacing it. So
friends, these were some of the add-on and
their benefits. The best thing is that
whenever you want insurance, that too comprehensive, do
take some add-ons and comments as per your need.